[Music]
idea cafe is our first project we are
meeting live on Fridays at 11:00 a.m.
Pacific Standard Time to move forward
with the together text first project the
idea Cafe when we get stuck at a point
we might move on to a different project
but right now that is what we were doing
we're figuring out what features it
needs to have how we fund it how it can
be an effective communication tool how
we grow the YouTube channel which is its
current iteration its own channel idea
cafe where I'm hosting conversations
that are going to be similar to the
format anyone can come and participate
in but not have it live on YouTube not
have it be something that potentially
millions of people can see it'll be up
to the individual participating how
comfortable they are clicking off or
dismissing different features right do
you want it recorded do not want to
record it do you want it video do you
want it voice and picking conversations
that matter not small talk conversations
about racism gender current events
creating a better world doing the
interpersonal work doing the intra
person at work anything that's
meaningful to you as an individual and
there can be a question designed for
that other people want to have a
conversation as well that is what the
idea Cafe will be anyone can come on say
when their availability is say what
their interests are and find people to
have a conversation with you don't need
to bring your existing friends we will
assign you people to talk to and we will
figure out the conflict together we will
figure out how to grow from conflict
we'll figure out how to mitigate
conflict so that you don't ever have to
everyone is welcome
we're not gonna kick people out
hopefully unless they're absolutely
horrific and I don't know what that
level is yet we don't know what that
level is yet but as people come and they
have an account and they're not being
trolls and they're being their true self
and just because we don't get along
doesn't mean I get to decide you're not
in anyone's table I can say you don't
get to sit at my table when the tools
and technology allow us to do that when
we're able to block people or say the
kinds of people we want to stay with in
the kinds of people we don't want to sit
with
but right now it's not right now it's
are you available at the same time in
the same place let's get together and
have a virtual conversation on the idea
cafe and we're creating it in full
transparency where anyone can come and
participate we were going to crowdfund
it together we're going to figure out
the features together and then once we
have that the tool for a conversation we
can use that tool to create all of the
other tools as well as have
conversations that are nothing to do
with technology nothing to do with
creating the new tools that are that
interpersonal work that are figure you
know how to have conversations about
difficult questions and difficult things
that are happening in the world what's
happening right now just divides us
being on opposite sides are you left are
you right are you this are you that how
dare you be that without me being able
to hear you hear yours why why does that
matter to you because the why and our
needs are often the same it's the
emotions we stack on top of that the
reasons we stack on top of that and the
other reen of people that makes this
combative culture that is going to
become more and more divisive unless we
create the tools to make it less and
less divisive and that's what the idea
cafe aims to be so come help create it
at 11:00 a.m. on Fridays Pacific
Standard Time thanks